GEDE PUTU ADYATMA PUTRA

♦ 081292456414 **★** gedeputu406@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/gede-putu-adyatma-putra-3916561a0/

O JI Cempaka no 90, Kp Bulak Jatiasih



Objektif

I am a Informatics student at gunadarma university who is still studying here for 4 years. I have experience at Bangkit Academy 2024 Mobile Development Learning path, and being an informatics engineering laboratory assistant at Gunadarma University by teaching object-based programming using the java programming language.

PENDIDIKAN

SMA Tulus Bhakti / Sma/Sederajat IPA /

Jatiasih / 2018 - 2021

Universitas Gunadarma / Sarjana Informatika /

Kalimalang / 2021 - Sekarang

PENGALAMAN KERJA

Informatic Engineering Labolatory Assistan | Assistant Labolatory | Pegawai Kontrak

Universitas Gunadarma | Maret 2024 - Sekarang

I started teaching the students about object-based programming using the java programming language. Regularly organize and deliver materials and give assignments at every weekly meeting held in the laboratory room. I also gave assessments to the students who followed the material from other teachers.

Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, & Traveloka Android Development Cohort | Mobile Development | Pegawai Kontrak

Bangkit Academy | Februari 2024 - Juli 2024

During the 5 months of participating in the activities of Bangkit Academy, I gained learning and experience about making android-based mobile applications using the Kotlin programming language. at Bangkit Academy I participated in learning and working on projects in teams, containing 7 members including me.

SERTIFIKASI

- Pengembangan Aplikasi Android Intermediate, Dicoding Indonesia, Nomor: 10P8W47NLXQK, 2024
- Fundamental Aplikasi Android, Dicoding Indonesia, Nomor: 72ZDY13G9ZYW, 2024
- Sertificate Of Completion Bangkit, Bangkit Academy, Nomor: -, 2024
- Memulai Dasar Pemrograman untuk Menjadi Pengembang Software, Dicoding Indonesia, Nomor: 53XEY144VPRN, 2024

SKILL

Hard Skill : Mobile Development, Programmer Soft Skill : Teaching Labolatory, Communication

Software Skill: Java language programming, Kotlin language programming, Excel, HTML, CSS